we haven't loved each other well Ah now it's not
no nos hemos querido bien Ah ahora no es
her fault now the fault is
culpa de ella ahora la culpa es de los
both of us we haven't loved each other well in plural
dos no nos hemos querido bien en plural
TR these types of things disgust me a lot
TR este tipo de cosas me dan muchísimo
because she knows that she has done
asco porque ella sabe que ha hecho mal
things wrong not her Raúl not Auron but
las cosas ella no Raúl no auron sino
her it was something quite complicated
ella fue algo bastante complicado por
because we are two very different people
porque somos dos personas muy distintas
in terms of being and thinking of
en forma de ser y en forma de pensar
course he thinks that you have to be faithful and
claro él piensa que hay que ser fiel y
you the complete opposite there were things from his
tú todo lo contrario había cosas de su
past that I needed him to close
pasado que yo necesitaba que que cerrase
here the only thing from the past that he could be
aquí la única cosa del pasado que puede
talking about is basically his
estar hablando es básicamente su
relationship with Vin with Sara his ex-girlfriend
relación con vin con Sara su exnovia
for a decade with which what
durante una década con lo cual lo que
she wanted to do is for Auron to make
ella quería hacer es que auron hiciera
public the breakup he had with his
pública la ruptura que tuvo con su
ex-girlfriend which seems to me to be the most repulsive thing
exnovia cosa que me parece las cosas más